New England Medical Center Records MS099
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Administration records, 1929 -- 1994; MS099.003; 67.2 Linear Feet
  - Viola J. Spinelli files, 1948 -- 1980; 1971 -- 1976; MS099.003.002; 10.8 Linear Feet
    - Quarles, John R., 1969 -- 1973; MS099.003.002.205.00011 (Box 205)
    - Public Relations Search Committee, 1972; MS099.003.002.205.00012 (Box 205)
    - Quigley, John, 1972 -- 1974; MS099.003.002.205.00013 (Box 205)
    - Quincy School Community Council, 1969 -- 1974; MS099.003.002.205.00014 (Box 205)
    - Quincy School Project, 1970 -- 1971; MS099.003.002.205.00015 (Box 205)
    - Quincy School Complex, 1969; MS099.003.002.205.00016 (Box 205)
    - Relationships between pediatrics and surgery, ad hoc committee, 1967 -- 1968; MS099.003.002.205.00017 (Box 205)
    - South Boston Community Health Board, 1970; MS099.003.002.206.00001 (Box 206)
    - South End Business Men's Association, 1968 -- 1975; MS099.003.002.206.00002 (Box 206)
    - Department of Surgery (Special Committee), 1973 -- 1974; MS099.003.002.206.00003 (Box 206)
    - Surgical Executive Committee, 1974; MS099.003.002.206.00004 (Box 206)
    - Architects Collaborative, 1966 -- 1967; MS099.003.002.206.00005 (Box 206)
    - Consultation program for elective surgery, 1974; MS099.003.002.206.00006 (Box 206)
    - Surgery, search committee, 1975; MS099.003.002.206.00007 (Box 206)
  - General files, 1929 -- 1994; MS099.003.003; 57.6 Linear Feet
    - T-NEMC Master Plan report, 1970; MS099.003.003.018.00003; Architects Collaborative, Inc.; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 18)
    - NEMCH: Planning Guide Section I, 1965; MS099.003.003.018.00004; Viguers, Richard T. (Box 18)
    - NEMCH: Planning Guide Section II, 1966; MS099.003.003.018.00005; Viguers, Richard T.; Spinelli, Viola J. (Box 18)
    - Organization - Hospital, 1961 -- 1979; MS099.003.003.018.00006 (Box 18)
    - NEMCH: organization meeting and dinner, 1965; MS099.003.003.018.00007 (Box 18)
    - Planning Guide draft no. 3, 1965; MS099.003.003.018.00008 (Box 18)
    - T-NEMC Functions List, 1965 -- 1966; MS099.003.003.018.00009 (Box 18)
    - Planning Guide for the NECH, 1965; MS099.003.003.018.00010 (Box 18)
    - Planning Guide, 1965; MS099.003.003.018.00011 (Box 18)
    - NEMCH: Integration Book, 1965; MS099.003.003.018.00012; Viguers, Richard T. (Box 18)
    - NEMCH: Planning Guide Volume V, 1965; MS099.003.003.018.00013; Viguers, Richard T. (Box 18)
    - NEMCH Hospital Council, agenda and minutes, 1965 -- 1970; MS099.003.003.018.00014 (Box 18)
    - NEMCH Hospital Council, agenda and minutes, 1965 -- 1968; MS099.003.003.018.00015 (Box 18)
    - NEMCH Hospital Council, agenda and minutes, 1968 -- 1971; MS099.003.003.018.00016 (Box 18)
    - NEMCH Hospital Council, agenda and minutes, 1972 -- 1973; MS099.003.003.018.00017 (Box 18)
    - NEMCH: trustees, members, and Board of Governors minutes - volume I, 1965 -- 1966; MS099.003.003.018.00018 (Box 18)
    - NEMCH: trustees, members, and Board of Governors minutes - volume II, 1966 -- 1968; MS099.003.003.019.00001 (Box 19)
    - NEMCH: trustees, members, and Board of Governors minutes - volume III, 1968 -- 1970; MS099.003.003.019.00002 (Box 19)
    - NEMCH: trustees, members, and Board of Governors minutes - volume IV, 1970 -- 1972; MS099.003.003.019.00003 (Box 19)
    - NEMCH: trustees, members, and Board of Governors minutes - volume V, 1972 -- 1974; MS099.003.003.019.00004 (Box 19)
    - NEMCH: annual meeting minutes, 1970 -- 1971; MS099.003.003.019.00005 (Box 19)
    - NEMCH: annual meeting minutes, 1973 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.019.00006 (Box 19)
    - NEMCH: annual meeting minutes, 1976 -- 1977; MS099.003.003.019.00007 (Box 19)
    - NEMC Board of Trustees, 1986; MS099.003.003.019.00008 (Box 19)
    - NEMC Board of Trustees, 1987; MS099.003.003.019.00009 (Box 19)
    - NEMC Board of Governors, 1987; MS099.003.003.019.00010 (Box 19)
    - Boston City Hospital, 1981 -- 1982; MS099.003.003.019.00011 (Box 19)
    - Boston Redevelopment Authority, 1975 -- 1984; MS099.003.003.019.00012 (Box 19)
    - Boston University Medical Center, 1981 -- 1982; MS099.003.003.019.00013 (Box 19)
    - Boston University School of Management - Attitude Survey, 1977; MS099.003.003.019.00014 (Box 19)
    - Chinese, 1981 -- 1983; MS099.003.003.020.00001 (Box 20)
    - Chinese Culture Institute, 1981 -- 1986; MS099.003.003.020.00002 (Box 20)
    - Chinese Development Economic Council - Advisory Investment Board, 1980; MS099.003.003.020.00003 (Box 20)
    - Connecticut Mutual Life, 1981; MS099.003.003.020.00004 (Box 20)
    - Corporate Reorganization, 1982 -- 1983; MS099.003.003.020.00005 (Box 20)
    - Corporate Reorganization - NEMC Real Estate Co., 1983; MS099.003.003.020.00006 (Box 20)
    - Council of Deans, 1981 -- 1985; MS099.003.003.020.00007 (Box 20)
    - Gerontology, 1980 -- 1983; MS099.003.003.020.00008 (Box 20)
    - Laboratory Technician Course, 1951 -- 1982; MS099.003.003.020.00009 (Box 20)
    - Neurology, Department of, 1973 -- 1983; MS099.003.003.020.00010 (Box 20)
    - Physician-in-Chief Fund, 1964 -- 1985; MS099.003.003.020.00011 (Box 20)
    - Posner Hall (background), 1971 -- 1979; MS099.003.003.020.00012 (Box 20)
    - Psychiatry, 1979 -- 1983; MS099.003.003.020.00013 (Box 20)
    - Public Health Department Annual Reports, 1969 -- 1978; MS099.003.003.020.00014 (Box 20)
    - Quality Control - Susan Bailis, 1985; MS099.003.003.020.00015 (Box 20)
    - School of Nursing, 1977 -- 1984; MS099.003.003.020.00016 (Box 20)
    - Ropes & Grey general correspondence, 1981 -- 1984; MS099.003.003.020.00017 (Box 20)
    - Security, 1976 -- 1980; MS099.003.003.020.00018 (Box 20)
    - Saint Elizabeth's Hospital, 1977 -- 1984; MS099.003.003.020.00019 (Box 20)
    - Saint James Church, 1982; MS099.003.003.020.00020 (Box 20)
    - Saint Margaret's Hospital, 1980; MS099.003.003.020.00021 (Box 20)
    - Shawmut Bank, 1985; MS099.003.003.020.00022 (Box 20)
    - Sleep unit, 1982; MS099.003.003.020.00023 (Box 20)
    - Social Service, 1980 -- 1983; MS099.003.003.020.00024 (Box 20)
    - Boston Private Industry Council, Inc., 1980 -- 1982; MS099.003.003.020.00025 (Box 20)
    - Boston Emergency Medical Center (BEMC), 1981; MS099.003.003.020.00026 (Box 20)
    - Children's Hospital Medical Center, 1984; MS099.003.003.020.00027 (Box 20)
    - President's reports, 1976 -- 1978; MS099.003.003.020.00028 (Box 20)
      Reports of President of NEMC Board of Trustees members.
    - Dr. Proger - memorandums, 1970 -- 1980; MS099.003.003.064.00001 (Box 64)
    - B.A.F. TV program, 1965; MS099.003.003.064.00002 (Box 64)
    - Posner hall agreement with NEMC, 1971 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.064.00003 (Box 64)
    - NEMC, Private Practice and the New England Center Hospital, 1954; MS099.003.003.064.00004 (Box 64)
    - Proger list of publications, MS099.003.003.064.00005 (Box 64)
    - NEMC, Medical Practice and Academic Medicine in the New England Center Hospital, 1956; MS099.003.003.064.00006 (Box 64)
    - Watergate, 1973; MS099.003.003.064.00007 (Box 64)
    - Eulogy - Dr. Thannhauser, 1962; MS099.003.003.064.00008 (Box 64)
    - B - miscellaneous, 1959; MS099.003.003.064.00009 (Box 64)
    - Dr. Proger - memorandums, 1970 -- 1971; MS099.003.003.064.00010 (Box 64)
    - Address to the graduating class, Tufts University School of Medicine, 1972; MS099.003.003.064.00011 (Box 64)
    - Comments on medical education, second year medicine year book, 1961 -- 1963; MS099.003.003.064.00012 (Box 64)
    - NEMC, Some Comments on the Role of the New England Center Hospital in the General Medical Scene, 1953; MS099.003.003.064.00013 (Box 64)
    - Fifth World Congress of Cardiology - India, 1966; MS099.003.003.064.00014 (Box 64)
    - Some Comments on Planning, 1962; MS099.003.003.064.00015 (Box 64)
    - Memoranda, 1939 -- 1970; MS099.003.003.064.00016 (Box 64)
    - University and hospital, 1944; MS099.003.003.064.00017 (Box 64)
    - Astwood, Edwin, 1957; MS099.003.003.064.00018 (Box 64)
    - Berkman, 1960 -- 1971; MS099.003.003.064.00019 (Box 64)
    - Astwood, Edwin, 1962 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.064.00020 (Box 64)
    - Article and notes, 1971; MS099.003.003.064.00021 (Box 64)
    - Miscellaneous old correspondence, 1962 -- 1964; MS099.003.003.064.00022 (Box 64)
    - Nathanson, Larry, 1967 -- 1971; MS099.003.003.064.00023 (Box 64)
    - Hallowell, Burton, 1967 -- 1975; MS099.003.003.064.00024 (Box 64)
    - Tufts AOA, 1970 -- 1977; MS099.003.003.064.00025 (Box 64)
    - Britten, Anthony, 1967 -- 1971; MS099.003.003.064.00026 (Box 64)
    - Callow, Allan, 1958 -- 1965; MS099.003.003.064.00027 (Box 64)
    - Cassidy, Carl, 1958 -- 1971; MS099.003.003.064.00028 (Box 64)
    - Calisti, Dean Louis, 1967 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.064.00029 (Box 64)
    - Crosby, William, 1964 -- 1971; MS099.003.003.064.00030 (Box 64)
    - Deterling, Ralph, 1959 -- 1970; MS099.003.003.064.00031 (Box 64)
    - Essig, Alvin, 1965 -- 1970; MS099.003.003.064.00032 (Box 64)
    - Fanburg, Barry, 1967 -- 1971; MS099.003.003.064.00033 (Box 64)
    - Gellis, Sydney, 1967 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.064.00034 (Box 64)
    - Hayman, Dean Joesph Jr., 1955 -- 1957; MS099.003.003.064.00035 (Box 64)
    - Hill, Lawrence, 1975 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.064.00036 (Box 64)
    - Jeghers, Harold, 1966 -- 1971; MS099.003.003.064.00037 (Box 64)
    - Messer, Joseph, 1962 -- 1970; MS099.003.003.064.00038 (Box 64)
    - Proger speaking engagements and grand rounds, 1961 -- 1966; MS099.003.003.064.00039 (Box 64)
    - Millis, John, 1971 -- 1972; MS099.003.003.064.00040 (Box 64)
    - Mitus, W.J., 1968 -- 1969; MS099.003.003.064.00041 (Box 64)
    - Naimi, Shapur, 1961 -- 1969; MS099.003.003.064.00042 (Box 64)
    - Parnes, Leo, 1968 -- 1971; MS099.003.003.064.00043 (Box 64)
    - Raben, Maurice, 1953 -- 1977; MS099.003.003.064.00044 (Box 64)
    - Rahal, James, 1968; MS099.003.003.064.00045 (Box 64)
    - Rogers, Joseph, 1949 -- 1968; MS099.003.003.064.00046 (Box 64)
    - Simmons, Henry, 1967; MS099.003.003.064.00047 (Box 64)
    - Schwartz, Robert, 1966 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.064.00048 (Box 64)
    - Schwartz, William, 1976 -- 1977; MS099.003.003.064.00049 (Box 64)
    - Sokolow, Maurice, 1968 -- 1980; MS099.003.003.064.00050 (Box 64)
    - Solomon, David, 1952 -- 1980; MS099.003.003.064.00051 (Box 64)
    - Stearns, Norman, 1978; MS099.003.003.064.00052 (Box 64)
    - Watson, C., 1953; MS099.003.003.064.00053 (Box 64)
    - Miller, Harry, 1957; MS099.003.003.064.00054 (Box 64)
    - Weinstein, Louis, 1956 -- 1975; MS099.003.003.064.00055 (Box 64)
    - Weintraub, Lewis, 1964 -- 1969; MS099.003.003.064.00056 (Box 64)
    - Wolff, Sheldon, 1980 -- 1981; MS099.003.003.064.00057 (Box 64)
    - Ziskind, Jacob, correspondence, 1948 -- 1949; MS099.003.003.064.00058 (Box 64)
    - Sokolow, Maurice, 1954 -- 1966; MS099.003.003.064.00059 (Box 64)
    - Ziskind dedication correspondence, 1958 -- 1959; MS099.003.003.064.00060 (Box 64)
    - Patient correspondence, Jerome Grossman, 1981 -- 1988; MS099.003.003.159 (Box 159)
    - Staff appointments, 1972 -- 1978; MS099.003.003.205.00001 (Box 205)
    - Staff loan fund, 1967 -- 1977; MS099.003.003.205.00002 (Box 205)
    - Medical staff questionnaire, 1978; MS099.003.003.205.00003 (Box 205)
    - Staff Executive Committee, 1970 -- 1973; MS099.003.003.205.00004 (Box 205)
    - NEMCH house staff, 1965 -- 1971; MS099.003.003.205.00005 (Box 205)
    - Medical staff, 1966 -- 1969; MS099.003.003.205.00006 (Box 205)
    - Medical staff, 1970 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.205.00007 (Box 205)
    - Finance committee meeting, 1981; MS099.003.003.207.00005 (Box 207)
    - Biewend, Cameron, 1960 -- 1977; MS099.003.003.207.00006 (Box 207)
    - Harvard Community Health Plan (Finance Committee, 1978 -- 1980; MS099.003.003.207.00007 (Box 207)
    - Patient correspondence, 1979 -- 1980; MS099.003.003.207.00008 (Box 207)
    - Comments on the system of internal accounting control and related financial matters, 1975 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.207.00009 (Box 207)
    - Report on study of financial information and control systems, 1975; MS099.003.003.207.00010 (Box 207)
    - NEMCH: case reports, 1980; MS099.003.003.207.00011 (Box 207)
    - Metropolitan property, 1970 -- 1978; MS099.003.003.207.00012 (Box 207)
    - Music Hall Renovation Study, 1975; MS099.003.003.207.00013; Boston Redevelopment Authority (Box 207)
    - HCHP financial statements, 1980; MS099.003.003.207.00014 (Box 207)
    - HCHP financial statements, 1979 -- 1980; MS099.003.003.207.00015 (Box 207)
    - Music Hall Volume II, 1977 -- 1980; MS099.003.003.207.00016 (Box 207)
    - Proposed management letter comments, 1979; MS099.003.003.208.00001 (Box 208)
    - NEMCH: Application for mortgage insurance, 1975; MS099.003.003.209.00001 (Box 209)
      Volume 1
    - NEMCH: Application for mortgage insurance, 1977 -- 1978; MS099.003.003.209.00002 (Box 209)
      Volume 3
    - NEMCH: Application for mortgage insurance, 1978; MS099.003.003.209.00003 (Box 209)
      Volume 2, appendix 1
    - NEMCH: Application for mortgage insurance, 1975 -- 1978; MS099.003.003.209.00004 (Box 209)
      Volume 2, appendix 2
    - NEMCH: Application for mortgage insurance, 1975; MS099.003.003.209.00005 (Box 209)
      Volume 2, appendix 3
    - NEMCH: Application for mortgage insurance, 1975 -- 1978; MS099.003.003.209.00006 (Box 209)
      Volume 2, appendix 4
    - NEMCH: Application for mortgage insurance, 1978; MS099.003.003.209.00007 (Box 209)
      Volume 4
    - Tufts association HMO feasibility report and planning grant application, 1979; MS099.003.003.209.00008 (Box 209)
    - Council of Teaching Hospitals directory, educational programs and services, 1980; MS099.003.003.209.00009 (Box 209)
    - NEMCH rate schedule, 1980; MS099.003.003.209.00010 (Box 209)
    - NEMCH cash flow enhancement project, 1978; MS099.003.003.209.00011 (Box 209)
    - Music Hall II, 1977; MS099.003.003.210.00001 (Box 210)
    - MNA campaign, 1975 -- 1977; MS099.003.003.210.00002 (Box 210)
    - Construction approval - Cath. Lab, 1972; MS099.003.003.210.00003 (Box 210)
    - Tufts 750 mini school, 1973 -- 1975; MS099.003.003.210.00004 (Box 210)
    - United Community Service, 1973 -- 1977; MS099.003.003.210.00005 (Box 210)
    - Visiting Nurse Association of Boston, 1974 -- 1975; MS099.003.003.210.00006 (Box 210)
    - Chinatown Boston Redevelopment Study, 1971; MS099.003.003.210.00007 (Box 210)
    - Boston Chinese Community Health Facility: A Proposal, 1971; MS099.003.003.210.00008 (Box 210)
    - Economic Development for Boston's Chinese Community, 1974; MS099.003.003.210.00009 (Box 210)
    - Construction Kitchen Certificate of Need, 1972; MS099.003.003.210.00010 (Box 210)
    - Construction Approval, B.D. operating room, 1973; MS099.003.003.210.00011 (Box 210)
    - Construction Approval, Animal Research Facility, 1973; MS099.003.003.210.00012 (Box 210)
    - Construction Approval, Neutron Beam, 1974 -- 1975; MS099.003.003.210.00013 (Box 210)
    - Construction Approval, South Boston Day Hospital, 1975; MS099.003.003.210.00014 (Box 210)
    - Construction Approval, North Dorchester Day Hospital, 1975; MS099.003.003.210.00015 (Box 210)
    - Construction Approval, D. Street Day Care Program, 1975; MS099.003.003.210.00016 (Box 210)
    - Construction Approval, Radiology Lab, 1973; MS099.003.003.210.00017 (Box 210)
    - Construction Approval, Neurath's Computer, 1972 -- 1973; MS099.003.003.210.00018 (Box 210)
    - Construction Approval, Psychiatry, 1973; MS099.003.003.210.00019 (Box 210)
    - Construction Approval, Bay Cove Mental Health Center, 1975; MS099.003.003.210.00020 (Box 210)
    - Construction Approval, Student-Employee Health Service, 1974; MS099.003.003.210.00021 (Box 210)
    - Construction Approval: Blood Bank, 1972 -- 1973; MS099.003.003.210.00022 (Box 210)
    - Construction Approval, Day Hospital, 1974 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.210.00023 (Box 210)
    - Construction Approval, Radiology, 1974 -- 1975; MS099.003.003.210.00024 (Box 210)
    - Construction Phase 1A, 1968 -- 1971; MS099.003.003.210.00025 (Box 210)
    - Construction Phase 1A, 1972 -- 1973; MS099.003.003.210.00026 (Box 210)
    - Construction 1A space, 1971 -- 1973; MS099.003.003.210.00027 (Box 210)
    - Manzo, John, 1970 -- 1975; MS099.003.003.210.00028 (Box 210)
    - NEMCH Facilities Development Program, 1970 -- 1974; MS099.003.003.210.00029 (Box 210)
    - Construction 1A utilities center, 1968 -- 1972; MS099.003.003.211.00001 (Box 211)
    - Construction 1A furnishings, 1971 -- 1972; MS099.003.003.211.00002 (Box 211)
    - NECH staff executive meetings, 1966; MS099.003.003.211.00003 (Box 211)
    - Personnel requisitions, 1978; MS099.003.003.211.00004 (Box 211)
    - Personnel requisitions, 1978; MS099.003.003.211.00005 (Box 211)
    - Personnel requisitions management committee, 1966; MS099.003.003.211.00006 (Box 211)
    - Personnel requisitions, 1978; MS099.003.003.211.00007 (Box 211)
    - Patient questionnaire, miscellaneous, 1963 -- 1970; MS099.003.003.211.00008 (Box 211)
    - Construction funds, sources of, 1959 -- 1975; MS099.003.003.211.00009 (Box 211)
    - Construction phase 1B, 1969 -- 1972; MS099.003.003.211.00010 (Box 211)
    - Construction 1B: minutes, 1971 -- 1973; MS099.003.003.211.00011 (Box 211)
    - Conference on Boston Teaching Hospitals, comprehensive data, 1974; MS099.003.003.211.00012 (Box 211)
    - Conference of Boston Teaching Hospitals, 1974; MS099.003.003.211.00013 (Box 211)
    - Communications, current problems, 1973; MS099.003.003.211.00014 (Box 211)
    - Community and ambulatory care, 1973 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.211.00015 (Box 211)
    - Community health 1B community advisory committee packet, 1974; MS099.003.003.211.00016 (Box 211)
    - Community organization to discuss 1B, 1974; MS099.003.003.211.00017 (Box 211)
    - Computer search, 1975; MS099.003.003.211.00018 (Box 211)
    - Computer center, 1971 -- 1972; MS099.003.003.211.00019 (Box 211)
    - Code 100, 1967; MS099.003.003.211.00020 (Box 211)
    - Code 99, 1970; MS099.003.003.211.00021 (Box 211)
    - Clinical Study Unit, 1974 -- 1977; MS099.003.003.212.00001 (Box 212)
    - Chinese Consolidated Benevolent Association Negotiating Committee, 1972 -- 1974; MS099.003.003.212.00002 (Box 212)
    - Free Chinatown, 1971; MS099.003.003.212.00003 (Box 212)
    - Chinese Community Health Projects Committee, 1970 -- 1972; MS099.003.003.212.00004 (Box 212)
    - Chinese Community Evening Clinic and miscellaneous, 1971; MS099.003.003.212.00005 (Box 212)
    - 1B community organization, 1974; MS099.003.003.212.00006 (Box 212)
    - Anesthesia Search Committee, 1972 -- 1974; MS099.003.003.212.00007 (Box 212)
    - Animal Care Appreciation Day, 1974; MS099.003.003.212.00008 (Box 212)
    - Associate Executive Director Candidates, 1977; MS099.003.003.212.00009 (Box 212)
    - Boston City Hospital Pediatric Situation, 1976; MS099.003.003.212.00010 (Box 212)
    - C and E accounts, 1973; MS099.003.003.212.00011 (Box 212)
    - Champus: Civilian Health and Medical Program Informed Services, 1975 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.212.00012 (Box 212)
    - Chemistry Laboratory Renovation, 1975; MS099.003.003.212.00013 (Box 212)
    - American College of Surgeons, 1968 -- 1969; MS099.003.003.212.00014 (Box 212)
    - American College of Hospital Administrators, 1965 -- 1975; MS099.003.003.212.00015 (Box 212)
    - Ambulatory Search Committee, 1975; MS099.003.003.212.00016 (Box 212)
    - Administrative staff meetings agenda, 1974 -- 1975; MS099.003.003.212.00017 (Box 212)
    - Administrative on-call book, 1969 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.212.00018 (Box 212)
    - Administrative conferences, 1971 -- 1972; MS099.003.003.212.00019 (Box 212)
    - Appreciation Day, 1974; MS099.003.003.212.00020 (Box 212)
    - Continuing Care Committee, 1974; MS099.003.003.212.00021 (Box 212)
    - Curran, Jean, 1970 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.212.00022 (Box 212)
    - Davidson, Sidney, 1964 -- 1974; MS099.003.003.212.00023 (Box 212)
    - Dermatology Search, 1973 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.212.00024 (Box 212)
    - Development search, 1977; MS099.003.003.213.00001 (Box 213)
    - Dimock Community Health Center, 1973; MS099.003.003.213.00002 (Box 213)
    - Dukakis, Michael, 1974; MS099.003.003.213.00003 (Box 213)
    - Greater Boston Hospital Association (Directors), 1971 -- 1975; MS099.003.003.213.00004 (Box 213)
    - Greater Boston Hospital Association (General), 1970 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.213.00005 (Box 213)
    - Hamilton Associates, 1972 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.213.00006 (Box 213)
    - Haussermann, O.W., Jr., 1956 -- 1974; MS099.003.003.213.00007 (Box 213)
    - Health Planning Council for Greater Boston, 1969 -- 1974; MS099.003.003.213.00008 (Box 213)
    - Hinsey Report, 1958; MS099.003.003.213.00009 (Box 213)
    - Hospital administration preceptorship, 1965 -- 1973; MS099.003.003.213.00010 (Box 213)
    - Hospital council agenda items, 1968 -- 1972; MS099.003.003.213.00011 (Box 213)
    - Hospital council miscellaneous correspondence, 1964 -- 1972; MS099.003.003.213.00012 (Box 213)
    - Hospital council Committee on Ambulatory Care, 1970; MS099.003.003.213.00013 (Box 213)
    - Hospital council ad hoc Committee on Medical Staff Organization, 1965 -- 1966; MS099.003.003.213.00014 (Box 213)
    - Hospital council Advisory Committee on Planning and Construction, 1965; MS099.003.003.213.00015 (Box 213)
    - Information concerning the current cost of hospital and professional services at New England Medical Center hospitals, 1971; MS099.003.003.213.00016 (Box 213)
    - The Extended Care Unit in a General Hospital: A Guide to Planning, Organization and Management, 1965; MS099.003.003.213.00017 (Box 213)
    - House Officers Association, 1968 -- 1975; MS099.003.003.213.00018 (Box 213)
    - House Officers Orientation Program, 1969 -- 1975; MS099.003.003.213.00019 (Box 213)
    - Inhalation Therapy Service, 1967 -- 1974; MS099.003.003.213.00020 (Box 213)
    - Johnson, Harold, 1961 -- 1972; MS099.003.003.213.00021 (Box 213)
    - Clinical Laboratory (Search Committee for Director), 1971 -- 1975; MS099.003.003.214.00001 (Box 214)
    - Integration NEMCH, 1960 -- 1965; MS099.003.003.214.00002 (Box 214)
    - Hospital Council ad hoc Committee on Comprehensive Care, 1965; MS099.003.003.214.00003 (Box 214)
    - Hospital Council Medical Advisory Board on Math and Com. Fac., 1965 -- 1967; MS099.003.003.214.00004 (Box 214)
    - Lemuel Shattuck Hospital Dr. Glidden Brooks, Superintendent, 1970; MS099.003.003.214.00005 (Box 214)
    - Lemuel Shattuck Hospital search committee, 1970 -- 1971; MS099.003.003.214.00006 (Box 214)
    - Lemuel Shattuck Hospital, 1973; MS099.003.003.214.00007 (Box 214)
    - Lemuel Shattuck Hospital survey, 1973; MS099.003.003.214.00008 (Box 214)
    - NEMCH license application, 1965 -- 1967; MS099.003.003.214.00009 (Box 214)
    - Maloney, William, 1972 -- 1974; MS099.003.003.214.00010 (Box 214)
    - Management Committee, 1970; MS099.003.003.214.00011 (Box 214)
    - Management Control Committee, 1973 -- 1974; MS099.003.003.214.00012 (Box 214)
    - Massachusetts, Commonwealth of Laboratory Licensure, 1968 -- 1971; MS099.003.003.214.00013 (Box 214)
    - Massachusetts, Commonwealth of Diagnostic X-ray Survey, 1967 -- 1971; MS099.003.003.214.00014 (Box 214)
    - Medical Foundation, Inc., 1971 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.214.00015 (Box 214)
    - Department of Medicine Review Committee, 1975 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.214.00016 (Box 214)
    - John S. Millis report, 1971 -- 1973; MS099.003.003.214.00017 (Box 214)
    - Mix, Martin, 1975; MS099.003.003.214.00018 (Box 214)
    - National Association of Children's Hospitals Annual meeting, 1973 -- 1975; MS099.003.003.214.00019 (Box 214)
    - National League for Nursing, 1970 -- 1974; MS099.003.003.214.00020 (Box 214)
    - Neurology Search Committee, 1974 -- 1976; MS099.003.003.214.00021 (Box 214)
    - Newton Wellesley Hospital, 1969 -- 1972; MS099.003.003.214.00022 (Box 214)